[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Don't leave me alone
Trembling in the dark night
SHENG 2026 CONCERT "DON'T LEAVE ME ALONE" HITS GLOBAL SUCCESS
I'm used to having you around
I really can't lose you
If you still love me
Can you hold me tight again?
Thank you all.
You are like family to me.
Without you, I wouldn't be here.
THE FIXERS
NIGHT AND DAY
Chao Ming-cheng dropped a bombshell at the Ming Young Party fundraiser today.
He shared a video of his son being framed by mobsters…
I'm so happy you came.
Dad dislikes it when I join.
Otherwise, I'd love attending these pretentious gatherings.
Keep your brother out of trouble.
It'll be fine.
Lucky, didn't I say you can't play with this one?
Go get another one.
Are you okay?
Did you get hurt?
-Have you been secretly practicing? -It's all about talent, okay?
Two years of practice.
Your brother beat you in just three months.
Use your two-handed backhand more.
You could've won sooner.
Dragging out a win is still a loss.
Do you hear me?
Good job.
Very good.
Keep it up.
Sir.
Oh, Tristan, come.
Meet the speaker.
Hello, sir.
This is Tristan.
Why didn't you say you were here?
You were all busy.
Not that busy.
Howie, time for breakfast!
Brooding heartthrob Sheng…
Tell me. Where did you go last night?
You used to flip through channels when you returned from a big score.
Did you get into trouble?
What trouble?
My biggest trouble in life is you.
Yeah, right.
Who could it be this early?
And you are?
I am looking for Felix Chiang.
Okay.
Felix.
-What? -It's for you.
How can I help you?
I am from Ching He.
I'd like you to come by.
I didn't donate that much last year.
You're far too kind to honor me like this.
Howie, eat your breakfast quickly. Don't be late for school.
Quite the big shot, Loach.
A cop car last time. A fancy car this time.
Milky, I don't have time today. I'll buy us tea next time.
Fuck your tea.
If you don't pay today, I won't fucking let you go.
How about you come with us to Ching He Temple for tea, Milky?
Who are you to interrupt my boss?
Shut up!
Sorry, sir. Kids don't know any better.
I'll get the door for you.
Please.
Don't whine. Be good.
Boss, who are they?
Your boss's boss, as in my boss, once told me
to stay far away from Ching He's men.
Loach is getting cooked this time.
Damn it.
Sir.
Hey.
The chairman of Ching He, Thackery Huang.
Thanks for your help last night.
Oh, sir.
Don't worry.
I won't mention it.
Nothing seals tighter than my lips.
Remember Sir Hong?
I can't even recall what I ate last night.
Over a decade ago,
San He sent you to protect Chamber Thirteen's leader, Black Bull.
But he was killed right under your nose.
The one who took him out
was me.
Sir,
I believe whatever you say.
But I really didn't know Black Bull. I'd never met him.
You have the wrong guy.
Hey.
Back when you and Chen Liang-chi used to fight for turf for San He,
nobody could rival you two.
You, in particular,
never killed anyone.
You only injured your opponents' kneecaps.
Sir,
I was just trying to make a living.
Over a decade has passed.
Your aim is as sharp as ever.
Is there a chance
that you'd work for us at Ching He?
Oh, no.
I'm no longer the same.
Besides, my hand…
Anyway, I really can't work for you.
From what I know, you've been in need of help lately.
If you come and work for us,
money is no object.
I don't think that's necessary.
I only want my family to be safe.
And please, don't come to my place again.
Like ships that pass in the night,
let's stay out of each other's sight.
Goodbye.
So,
should we look for someone else?
Give him some time.
He will come back.
Lucky.
Wait.
Okay.
No more.
The vet said you're on a diet.
Last one.
Superstar Sheng released his latest album, Fantastic Beast…
SHENG ANNOUNCES TAIPEI ARENA CONCERT
Lucky, sit.
Wait for me at home.
See you tonight.
Welcome.
Our bread is fresh out of the oven.
Sir, I'll have a three-in-one combo.
Pineapple, scallion, pork floss. One of each! Make them hot!
Feeling better?
I'm fine now.
It's nothing compared to before.
Fucking tough.
Your wife didn't ask anything?
Saw a hottie while riding my motorbike, and I crashed.
-She believed that? -Yeah.
Here.
I'm heading to school.
Hurry home after school.
Hello, sir.
It's bro.
Hello, bro.
What?
We need more salad dressing.
Oh, okay.
-What's this? -It's for your son.
Why didn't you give it to him just now?
It hits different coming from his dad.
Did they say who will replace me?
There's no one else.
They'll let me go solo for sure this time.
You know the chairman.
He'd never agree to anything against the rules.
CHING HE TEMPLE: EIGHT O'CLOCK TONIGHT
Chen Chia-yun.
Time to eat.
Don't you get sick of this?
You startled me.
What happened to you?
Got into a fight?
-It's a dog bite. -Dog bite?
Hey.
Your 70-to-30 golden ratio.
My ticket!
You got Sheng's face dirty.
It's all wet now.
What ticket? You're so uptight about it.
A concert ticket. It took me forever to get one.
Going with a guy?
No.
-You've got a boyfriend. -No.
"No."
This was in the mail. It's in English.
What is it?
An acceptance letter from the US exam board!
Seriously?
Hickory, dickory, dock. She's a chip off the old block!
You're in luck, buddy.
But I was just giving it a try. I don't have to go.
Don't worry about money. I will take care of it, okay?
This can wait until I graduate and save up.
Your dad and I never achieved much.
Luckily, you're smart like your mom.
Don't miss your chance.
I will figure out the money, all right?
Hello?
Hello, this is Hsing Tai Bank. Is this Mr. Chiang?
Yes, it is.
This is a courtesy reminder to make your loan payment for this month.
-It is overdue. -Go eat.
Please remit payment to prevent a negative impact on your credit score.
Okay, I understand.
Thank you.
Parkinson's disease?
How's that possible, Doctor?
I've never had any major illnesses.
I've only sprained my right hand.
Your situation is quite rare.
Besides resting hand tremors, you also have concurrent action tremors.
Then how is this disease treated?
Will my left hand also become like this?
This disease is caused by the degeneration of substantia nigra cells in the brain.
-Dopamine secretion… -Doctor, make it simple.
Simply put, it is usually incurable.
But active treatment with medication can slow down its progression.
Then…
Then, when it progresses,
what happens?
Some patients may develop disabilities or dementia in the final stages.
But the rate of progression varies.
Some progress from the initial to the final stage in just three months.
But if managed well, it could take ten years or more.
Sweetie,
when Howie's exams are done,
let's travel abroad.
I've never even taken you guys abroad.
The chairman says you can go in and see him now.
Okay.
Let me say this first. I won't do anything immoral.
Don't worry.
We are not killers or criminals.
We merely help people take care of problems.
This type of fish is called a janitor fish.
They usually hide in the murkiest waters.
No natural predators.
Extremely resilient.
But humans don't like them.
They find them dirty and smelly.
But without them,
the water would have long been polluted.
Ching He's fixers
are like this type of fish.
Whether it's high society
or the criminal underworld,
when someone runs into a problem they shouldn't handle themselves,
they hire us
to secretly clean it up for them.
We are above both sides of the law.
We don't favor either side.
Here, you don't go by your name.
Only a code name.
Oh. That's easy.
Others call me Swamp Eel.
CHING HE
Fixer code names come from the Thousand Character Classic.
Then what's mine?
Why is he here?
You again, jerk?
Listen, we still have a score to settle.
He's Fixer Gold.
-He'll be your partner from now on. -Why?
No way.
Only Fixer Shadow can tolerate your temper.
No other fixer wants to team up with you.
His kneecap is now injured.
It will take him at least half a year to recover.
I can handle jobs on my own.
I don't need a partner,
especially not dead weight.
Damn, are you looking down on me?
Fixers work in pairs.
That is the rule.
And I've decided.
Until Fixer Shadow returns,
you two will be partners.
CHING HE
Ching He has three rules.
Fixers must abide by them.
Sir Hong.
First,
in life or death,
fixers must not reveal any of Ching He's secrets.
Second, fixers must not disobey orders.
When on a mission,
unless recalled by Ching He,
fixers must not abandon their duties.
Third, fixers must not reveal their identity
or alter missions due to personal feelings.
So…
What happens if a fixer breaks the rules?
One word.
Death.
Get lost if you're afraid.
Who's afraid?
We play by the rules. Don't you know that?
The request this time is to erase her daughter's sex tape.
Who is the client?
A district prosecutor.
Yen Wen-chieh.
Ms. Yen's daughter filmed a sex video with the singer, Sheng,
while they were dating.
Now that they've broken up,
Ms. Yen is worried that the video may leak,
so she's hired Ching He to get rid of it.
You'll use this to communicate.
By the way, you haven't told me my code name.
Fixer Bottom.
I'll tell you after the mission.
Is this your car too?
Is being a fixer that lucrative?
You drive a different car every day.
Hey, I'm your partner now.
Don't think about ditching me.
Find a way to put this on Sheng, then try to take his phone.
And then?
I'll tell you later.
Okay, come on, let's go.
Fuck you.
Disloyal son of a bitch.
Damn it.
Trackers nowadays are so small.
It looks just like a button cell.
How do I get close to that Sheng guy?
BOOHOO, MY TICKET GOT DIRTY
SHENG
CHIA-YUN
Excuse me. Is the backstage area this way?
-Are you on staff? -No.
Only staff are allowed backstage.
Really?
The show has started. Please hurry.
Our entryway is designed to attract wealth.
As for fortune, we hired…
Can you cut the crap? Answer only when asked.
-Which way is up? -This way, please.
I'll call the elevator.
Who lives in this building?
Prominent figures like you. Just not as handsome.
Who lives above and below? Are they noisy?
Soundproofing is great here, but I can't disclose who they are.
I want to get a feel for the vibe in the living room.
Wait for me in there.
Don't come out until I call you.
I… Me?
-Yes. -Oh, okay, then…
Then…
Tell me if you need anything.
-Thank you. -Excuse me.
Thank you.
Watch out.
Hey.
Fixer Stealth, set up a proxy.
I'm busy. Working late, coding.
Cut the crap. I hacked his laptop with your program.
Not a damn thing in it.
I suspect he stores all the videos on his phone.
Can you hack into his phone?
The Trojan is in there, so…
You need to get his phone if you want to delete the videos from it.
First, send the surveillance footage from his mobile messaging app to me.
Sorry.
SHENG, ARTIST'S DRESSING ROOM
I'm here to fix the air conditioner.
Thank you.
You are like family to me.
Thank you all.
I will definitely come back.
I know he shouldn't turn it down,
but he must rest for at least a week after today's performance.
That's what the doctor said.
Listen, we need to think long-term.
Okay?
He's here. I'll call you.
That's all for now. Bye.
Are you okay?
Where are the fans?
At the exit passageway. I have someone keeping watch.
Sorry, we need to clear the room. Thanks.
Thank you. Sir.
We need to clear the room.
Okay, right away.
-Sorry. -Not at all.
Thank you.
So many people.
Add me.
Sheng, can you give me an autograph?
Right here.
Can you write "To Chia-yun"?
So handsome!
Excuse me. Give me an autograph.
Put it on my chest.
-Stay away, please. -I really like him. I have all his albums.
I really like you.
Thanks, folks.
Can I get an autograph, please?
-Thanks, folks. That's all for now. -Oh, come on.
Bye.
Let's catch him at the exit!
Felix Chiang!
Why are you here?
-You stole my ticket, didn't you? -No, listen.
You ruined it. I had to buy from a scalper!
Do you know how expensive it was?
Let me explain.
Since when are you a Sheng fan?
No.
Howie had midterms and couldn't come.
He asked me to get an autograph for him.
-Howie Chiang? -Yeah. His idol.
Hey, tell me.
What did he just whisper to you?
Just now?
-The album! -Hey!
That Sheng isn't a nice guy!
Don't forget your interview later.
I'm not going.
Get a hotel room for me.
But we've agreed to it. Last time--
I said I'm not going.
Close the door.
NANA
HI, IT'S SHENG. THANKS FOR COMING. FREE LATER?
GOT A NEW DROP TODAY
MUST BE NICE TO BE HANDSOME! WHAT KIND OF FAN IS IT?
FUCK! THE OBSESSIVE TYPE. SUPER FORWARD
WHERE ARE YOU UNWRAPPING IT?
THEY GOT MIRRORS
DON'T END UP IN THE NEWS LIKE DONG
FUCK, THANKS FOR CLEANING UP MY MESS, TAI!
BRING HER OVER FOR A FEW DRINKS NEXT TIME AFTER YOU'VE HAD YOUR FUN!
Hello, this is X Hotel. How can I help you?
Reserve a room on the top floor for me tonight.
Tell Mr. Yao that it's for Louis.
Sorry, we're fully booked today--
Tell Mr. Yao that it's for Mr. Hsueh's son.
-Got it? -Okay.
I have another call.
Send me a message when it's done.
Hello. Mission accomplished.
What's next?
You planted it on him?
What do you think? Easy-peasy.
Well, congratulations.
You can go home.
I worked hard to put the tracker on him. Don't you want me to follow him?
Who told you that was a tracker?
What was it, then?
A regular button cell.
A button cell?
Why did we need to put that on him?
Ask yourself.
You put it.
Damn it. I show you respect, and you piss me off.
Hey, where are you right now?
Hello?
Fuck.
Hey, hello? Chia-yun?
How dare you call me!
I have a question for you.
That Sheng guy.
Where is he going next?
Why do you ask?
Tell me first. I'll explain later. It's urgent.
He's going to X Hotel.
You're not a stan, are you?
How do you know he's going to a hotel? Did he tell you that?
Are you over there too?
I'm already home.
His stans track his every move.
But I'm not a stan.
What language are you speaking?
So you're not a fan. Whatever.
Uh, hello?
LET'S MEET AT X HOTEL, 3105
Mr. Yao, I want French cheese and sparkling water.
Two of each. Send them to my room.
Sure, I'll send them up right away.
Sorry for making you meet me here.
There are paparazzi at my place.
Getting snapped by the paparazzi
is quite exciting too.
Do you like to be photographed?
Roses are red, violets are blue
I'll take you down a peg or two
Found you.
Fuck. What a piece of cake.
Take this to the room across the hall.
-Just say it's from Mr. Yao. -Okay.
I didn't order this.
This is compliments of the hotel manager.
Hello, Stealth?
Get me information on everyone in Sheng's video-sharing group
as well as their backgrounds.
Just so you know, I'm heading out after this.
I keep working late, leaving my wife with the baby.
The sterilizer broke down. Guess how many bottles I washed?
What a unique necklace.
Don't you think…
doing it in front of the window
is more exciting?
Then…
have you ever tried…
filming while doing it?
That's even more exciting.
What a coincidence.
Same elevator again.
Who sent you here?
Give me the phone.
Going for the Taser?
Take it!
-Run now! -Run!
Hand over the phone.
If you want the phone, just say so.
Why shoot my tires? I just changed them, you know?
She wanted to destroy the phone too.
Seems we shared a goal.
I will relay this to the chairman.
Do you think she is from Yeh Yueh Tong?
It's possible.
But her style isn't quite like theirs.
She's not as ruthless.
Got it.
Take the phone to Ms. Yen first.
Felix Chiang,
you were quite clever for your first mission.
Hey. Speaking of this, I'm pissed.
This jerk tricked me with a button cell. Said it was a tracker.
Fortunately, I was two steps ahead.
I swapped his phone with mine.
I wanted to see what you were capable of, old man.
Wait, I now need to buy a new phone.
Can I get reimbursed?
Sure.
It seems like you two are getting along.
That's all for now. Go.
What made you think we're getting along?
This jerk…
I have to buy two new tires before I've even made a cent.
I'm paying to work here.
Listen, you're paying for the tires.
Goddamn it.
Ms. Yen, I have a child too.
I understand how you feel.
Hey, you mentioned Yeh Yueh Tong. Who are they?
You wouldn't understand.
Are you gonna tell me or not?
Their founder was kicked out of Ching He.
She started her own organization afterward
and stole a lot of Ching He's business.
I can't watch it anymore.
These aren't only videos of your daughter.
Delete all the videos, and no one can hurt them again.
It's confirmed. There are no other copies.
The files can't be restored.
Delete them all.
If this happened to my child,
I don't know what I would do.
Fixers aren't psychologists.
Save your excessive empathy for something else.
Damn it. You heartless bastard.
You didn't see that Sheng guy with your own eyes.
I'm pretty sure he does snow.
CHIA-YUN
Chen Chia-yun is gonna chew me out.
Hey, how did this happen?
Weren't all the videos deleted?
It's not Ms. Yen's daughter.
It's another victim.
You are like family to me.
Without you, I wouldn't be here.
DISGUSTING. DROP HIM.
SURELY SHE LURED HIM
I will definitely come back.
SHENG'S EXPLICIT VIDEO GOES VIRAL TATTOOED GIRL BELIEVED TO BE MODEL LIN
I don't care if you hire thugs or private investigators.
I have her handle.
Go find that woman for me!
Don't call the police.
You got that?
Yeh Yueh Tong hasn't even made a move yet,
and Ching He has already come knocking.
Madam Fan.
This is going to be interesting.
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu